Register of the Rodney Kennedy-Minott Papers, 1967-1994
Hoover Institution Archives
- Ambassador to Sweden office file, 1977-1980
  - 1978
    - Correspondence
      - Bergqvist, Bo (Box-folder 8: 25)
      - Bjerin, Ray, Mr. (Box-folder 8: 26)
      - Blake, James J., Honorable (Box-folder 8: 27)
      - Blum, Barbara, Ms. (Box-folder 8: 28)
      - Blumenberg, Ulf, Mr. (Box-folder 8: 29)
      - Boswich, John A., Jr., Dr. (Box-folder 8: 30)
      - Brewster, Kingman, Jr., Ambassador (Box-folder 8: 31)
      - Browaldh, Tore, Mr. (Box-folder 8: 32)
      - Brown, Chris, Mr. (Box-folder 8: 33)
      - Brown, Howard C., Dean (Box-folder 8: 34)
      - Brunsting, Carl, M.D. (Box-folder 8: 35)
      - Brzezinski, Zbigniew, Honorable (Box-folder 8: 36)
      - Buchanan, John H., Jr., M.C., Honorable (Box-folder 8: 37)
      - Burch, Donna Fay, Ms. (Box-folder 8: 38)
      - Burton, Phillip, Honorable (Box-folder 8: 39)
      - Butler, Landon, Esquire (Box-folder 8: 40)
      - Byron, Goodloe E., M.C. (Box-folder 8: 41)
      - Cameron, Robert B. (Box-folder 8: 42)
      - Caputo, Bruce, Honorable (Box-folder 8: 43)
      - Carl XVI Gustav and Silvia, King and Queen of Sweden (Box-folder 8: 44)
      - Carlson, Doris B., Mrs. (Box-folder 8: 45)
      - Chambers, Anne Cox (Box-folder 8: 46)
      - Chan, David B. (Box-folder 8: 47)
      - Charles, Alexandra (Box-folder 8: 48)
      - Cheek, Willard D. (Box-folder 8: 49)
      - Cherberg, John A. (Box-folder 8: 50)
      - Childs, Marquis, Mr. (Box-folder 8: 51)
      - Christopher, Warren, Honorable (Box-folder 8: 52)
      - Clay, William L., Honorable (Box-folder 8: 53)
      - Clough, Susan, Ms. (Box-folder 8: 54)
      - Cohen, Ralph S., Mr. (Box-folder 8: 55)
      - Cohen, William S., Honorable (Box-folder 8: 56)
      - Collie, Marvin K. (Box-folder 8: 57)
      - Conger, Clement E., Mr. (brochure is enclosed) (Box-folder 8: 58)
      - Connelly, Patrick S., Mr. (Box-folder 8: 59)
      - Connors, Eleanor, Ms. (Box-folder 8: 60)
      - Cooper, Kenneth, Prof. (Box-folder 8: 61)
      - Corin, Carl-Fredrik, Prof. (Box-folder 8: 62)
      - Costle, Douglas M. (Box-folder 8: 63)
      - Coughlan, Robert, Esquire (Box-folder 8: 64)
      - Cranston, Alan, Honorable (Box-folder 8: 65)
      - Dahlbeck, Nils, Dr. (Box-folder 8: 66)
      - Dean, Jonathan, Esquire (Box-folder 8: 67)
      - d'Hont, Michel M. (Box-folder 8: 68)
      - Dockens, William III, Prof. (Box-folder 8: 69)
      - Donaldson, Paul, Mr. (Box-folder 8: 70)
      - Doty, James, Mr. (Box-folder 8: 71)
      - Douglas, James H., Mr. (Box-folder 8: 72)
      - Dworen, Martin, Mr. (Box-folder 8: 73)
      - Edberry, Beynalf, Mr. and Mrs. (Box-folder 8: 74)
      - Eder, Joseph, Mr. (Box-folder 8: 75)
      - Ehrengren, Eric, Mr. (Box-folder 8: 76)
      - Ekman, Runar, Mr. (Box-folder 8: 77)
      - Elderkin, Lannie (Box-folder 8: 78)
      - Elmendorf, Fred, Mr. (Box-folder 8: 79)
      - Engel, Arthur A., Mr. (Box-folder 8: 80)
      - Ericson, Richard A., Jr., Honorable (Box-folder 8: 81)
      - Ewing, Nadine M., Ms. (Box-folder 8: 82)
      - Farrer-Baynes, William G., Mr. (Box-folder 8: 83)
      - Ferguson, Theodosia (Box-folder 8: 84)
      - Folkesson, Lars (Box-folder 8: 85)
      - Forsline, Tami, Ms. (Box-folder 8: 86)
      - Forssberg, Jarl G:son, Mr. (Box-folder 8: 87)
      - Franzen, Anders, Mr. (Box-folder 8: 88)
      - Fraser, Douglas A. (Box-folder 8: 89)
      - Free, James C. (Box-folder 8: 90)
      - Freeman, R.G. III (Box-folder 8: 91)
      - Fulbright, Betty (Box-folder 8: 92)
      - Fultz, Barbara, Ms. (Box-folder 8: 93)
      - Funseth, Robert, Mr. (Box-folder 8: 94)
      - Gerlach, Stefan, Mr. (Box-folder 9: 1)
      - Glasrud, Bruce, Prof. (Box-folder 9: 2)
      - Gomes, Danny, Mr. (Box-folder 9: 3)
      - Gomperts, Robert E. (Box-folder 9: 4)
      - Granum, Rex, Mr. (Box-folder 9: 5)
      - Graves, Ernest (Box-folder 9: 6)
      - Grothe, Peter, Mr. (Box-folder 9: 7)
      - Guillemin, Roger (Box-folder 9: 8)
      - Gushaw, Greg and Carol (Box-folder 9: 9)
      - Gyllenhammar, Pehr G. (Box-folder 9: 10)
      - Habib, Philip C., Esquire (Box-folder 9: 11)
      - Hagglund, John, The Honorable (Box-folder 9: 12)
      - Hagstrom, Tony, Mr. (Box-folder 9: 13)
      - Haig, Alexander, Jr., General and Mrs. (Box-folder 9: 14)
      - Halden, Folke, Mr. (Box-folder 9: 15)
      - Hamza, Aziz Abdelhamid, Ambassador (Box-folder 9: 16)
      - Hanley, James M., Honorable (Box-folder 9: 17)
      - Hanson, Heidi, Ms. (Box-folder 9: 18)
      - Hart, Gary, Honorable (Box-folder 9: 19)
      - Hasselblad, Erna, Mrs. (Box-folder 9: 20)
      - Hauge, Gabriel (telegrams are enclosed) (Box-folder 9: 21)
      - Hawkins, Augustus F., Honorable (Box-folder 9: 22)
      - Heckman, William, Jr., Mr. (Box-folder 9: 23)
      - Hedin, Sven Fredrik, Ambassador (Box-folder 9: 24)
      - Heinz, John H., III, Honorable (Box-folder 9: 25)
      - Heistein, B.J. (Box-folder 9: 26)
      - Heller, Clarence E. (Box-folder 9: 27)
      - Hensel, John, Mr. (Box-folder 9: 28)
      - Hernelius, Allan, Honorable (Box-folder 9: 29)
      - Hernod, Torsten, Mr. (Box-folder 9: 30)
      - Hill, Gordon C., Mr. (Box-folder 9: 31)
      - Hillys, Joe, Mr. (Box-folder 9: 32)
      - Himmelstrand, Ulf, Prof. (Box-folder 9: 33)
      - Hipp, Francis M., Mr. and Mrs. (Box-folder 9: 34)
      - Hoberman, Brian (Box-folder 9: 35)
      - Hoehler, William, Mr. (Box-folder 9: 36)
      - Hollenbeck, Harold C. Cap, Honorable (Box-folder 9: 37)
      - Holmberg, Eke, Prof. (Box-folder 9: 38)
      - Holy Cross College (Box-folder 9: 39)
      - Hook, Erik, Mr. (Box-folder 9: 40)
      - Hoppe, Rektor Gunnar (Box-folder 9: 41)
      - Hoyt, Mary (Box-folder 9: 42)
      - Hult, Bengt R., Mr. (Box-folder 9: 43)
      - Humphrey, Muriel, Honorable (Box-folder 9: 44)
      - Hunter, Robert, Esquire (Box-folder 9: 45)
      - Huttman, Elizabeth, Prof. (Box-folder 9: 46)
      - Huyser, Robert E., General and Mrs. (Box-folder 9: 47)
      - Hyde, Harold, Mr. (Box-folder 9: 48)
      - Ingervo, V. Seppo E., Mr. (Box-folder 9: 49)
      - Jackson, Richard L., Mr. (Box-folder 9: 50)
      - Janis, Jay (Box-folder 9: 51)
      - Jansson, Olle, Honorable (Box-folder 9: 52)
      - Jinnegerd, Eskil, Mr. (Box-folder 9: 53)
      - Johnson, Adeline, Mrs. (Box-folder 9: 54)
      - Johnson, James A. (Box-folder 9: 55)
      - Johnson, Leslie A., Ms. (Box-folder 9: 56)
      - Johnston, Bennett J., Honorable (Box-folder 9: 57)
      - Jones, David C., General (Box-folder 9: 58)
      - Jones, Edward C., Mr. (Box-folder 9: 59)
      - Jordan, Hamilton, Esquire (Box-folder 9: 60)
      - Jutterstrom, Christina (Box-folder 9: 61)
      - Katz, Sherman E., Mr. (Box-folder 9: 62)
      - Kidd, Isaac C., Jr., Admiral (Box-folder 9: 63)
      - King, Mary E., Ms. (Box-folder 9: 64)
      - Klick, Clifford C., Dr. (Box-folder 9: 65)
      - Kraft, Tim, Esquire (Box-folder 9: 66)
      - Kronmark, Eric, H.E. (Box-folder 9: 67)
      - Lees, Laurence F., Mr. (Box-folder 9: 68)
      - LeFante, Joseph, Honorable (Box-folder 9: 69)
      - Leifland, Leif, Honorable (Box-folder 9: 70)
      - Lerner, Louis A., Honorable (Box-folder 9: 71)
      - Leteus, Lars, Mr. (Box-folder 9: 72)
      - Levy, Hans W., Mr. (Box-folder 9: 73)
      - Lilliecreutz, Bengt, Mr. (Box-folder 9: 74)
      - Linder, Staffan Burenstam, Honorable (Box-folder 9: 75)
      - Link, Ruth, Ms. (Box-folder 9: 76)
      - Livingston, Robert Gerald, Mr. (Box-folder 9: 77)
      - Ljunggren, Anders, Mr. (Box-folder 9: 78)
      - Luetge, Bill, Mr. (Box-folder 9: 79)
      - Lukens, Alan W. (Box-folder 9: 80)
      - Lundqvist, Jorgen, Mr. (includes printed matter in Swedish) (Box-folder 9: 81)
      - Lundquist, Nils-H, Mr. (Box-folder 9: 82)
      - Lundsten, Ralph, Mr. (Box-folder 9: 83)
      - Lundstrom, Per (Box-folder 9: 84)
      - MacQueen, Bruce K. (Box-folder 9: 85)
      - Malek, Issa, Ambassador (Box-folder 9: 86)
      - Mann, James R., Honorable (Box-folder 9: 87)
      - Manshel, Warren D., Honorable (Box-folder 9: 88)
      - Martens, Robert J., Esquire (Box-folder 9: 89)
      - Mayo, Betty, Ms. (Box-folder 9: 90)
      - McCleary, Joel, Esquire (Box-folder 9: 91)
      - McCloskey, Paul N., Jr. (statement is enclosed) (Box-folder 9: 92)
      - McCune, Ellis E. (Box-folder 9: 93)
      - McDade, Joseph M., Honorable (Box-folder 9: 94)
      - Miller, Penny, Ms. (Box-folder 9: 95)
      - Minelli, Liza, Ms. (Box-folder 9: 96)
      - Mondale, Walter F., Honorable (Box-folder 9: 97)
      - Moore, Frank (Box-folder 9: 98)
      - Morse, Adriaen, Mr. (Box-folder 9: 99)
      - Montgomery, W.B., Mr. (Box-folder 9: 100)
      - Montouri, G.W. (Box-folder 9: 101)
      - Mottl, Ronald M., Honorable (Box-folder 9: 102)
      - Murelius, Olof, Mr. (Box-folder 9: 103)
      - Nelson, David, Mr. (Box-folder 10: 1)
      - Netter, Richard (Box-folder 10: 2)
      - Nilsson, Sam, Mr. (Box-folder 10: 3)
      - Nordbeck, Gunnar, Mr. (Box-folder 10: 4)
      - Norderdal, Gunnar, Mr. (Box-folder 10: 5)
      - Nordin, Magnus, Mr. (Box-folder 10: 6)
      - Nordquist, Kjell, Mr. (Box-folder 10: 7)
      - Norman, Anders, Mr. (Box-folder 10: 8)
      - Ochoa, Anthony, Professor and Mrs. (article is enclosed) (Box-folder 10: 9)
      - Odner, Sture (Box-folder 10: 10)
      - O'Konor, Louise (Box-folder 10: 11)
      - Olavarria, M. Luis Alberto, H.E. (Box-folder 10: 12)
      - O'Neill, Thomas P., Jr., Honorable (Box-folder 10: 13)
      - Onnesjo, Karl-Erik (Box-folder 10: 14)
      - Osterberg, Tom, Mr. (Box-folder 10: 15)
      - Ostlund, Kurt, Prof. (Box-folder 10: 16)
      - Owens, John, Mr. and Mrs. (Box-folder 10: 17)
      - Oyler, Soldanella, Ms. (Box-folder 10: 18)
      - Padgett, Dorothy, Ms. (Box-folder 10: 19)
      - Padilla, Joan (Box-folder 10: 20)
      - Palme, Rutger, Mr. (Box-folder 10: 21)
      - Pao, Yue-Kong, Sir (Box-folder 10: 22)
      - Patten, Edward J., Honorable (Box-folder 10: 23)
      - Patterson, Marjorie, Ms. (Box-folder 10: 24)
      - Paulsson, Bjorn, Mr. (Box-folder 10: 25)
      - Percy, Charles H., Honorable (Box-folder 10: 26)
      - Perkins, Dan, Mr. (Box-folder 10: 27)
      - Perry, Betsy (Box-folder 10: 28)
      - Perry, Jack (Box-folder 10: 29)
      - Perry, William J., Dr. (Box-folder 10: 30)
      - Persson, Jan, Dr. (Box-folder 10: 31)
      - Petersen, Jeffrey, His Excellency, Sir (Box-folder 10: 32)
      - Petersson, Hans, Mr. (Box-folder 10: 33)
      - Petree, Richard W. (Box-folder 10: 34)
      - Pettersson, John-Erik, Mr. (Box-folder 10: 35)
      - Phelan, James (Box-folder 10: 36)
      - Piscator, Per, Mr. (Box-folder 10: 37)
      - Poage, W.R., Congressman (Box-folder 10: 38)
      - Pursell, Carl Duanne, Honorable (Box-folder 10: 39)
      - Rabinowitch, Victor, Dr. (Box-folder 10: 40)
      - Rafshoon, Gerald, Esquire (Box-folder 10: 41)
      - Rainwater, Betty, Ms. (Box-folder 10: 42)
      - Ramel, Hans, Baron and Baroness (Box-folder 10: 43)
      - Ramel, Stig, Baron (Box-folder 10: 44)
      - Reed, J.V., Jr. (Box-folder 10: 45)
      - Reinhardt, John, Honorable (Box-folder 10: 46)
      - Revelius, Nils G. (Box-folder 10: 47)
      - Richanbach, Paul H., Mr. (Box-folder 10: 48)
      - Ridgway, Rozanne L., Ambassador (Box-folder 10: 49)
      - Rieman, Peter, Mr. (Box-folder 10: 50)
      - Rockefeller, David, Mr. (Box-folder 10: 51)
      - Roland, Aaron M. (Box-folder 10: 52)
      - Rostenkowski, Dan (Box-folder 10: 53)
      - Ruin, Olof, Prof. (Box-folder 10: 54)
      - Russell, Lawrence D., Esquire (Box-folder 10: 55)
      - Rylander, Jan, Mr. (Box-folder 10: 56)
      - Sagan, Ginetta (Box-folder 10: 57)
      - Samuels, Michael A., Mr. (Box-folder 10: 58)
      - Samuelson, Karl W., Mr. (Box-folder 10: 59)
      - Sawetamal, Suban, Ambassador (Box-folder 10: 60)
      - Sawhill, John C. (Box-folder 10: 61)
      - Schaefer, Philip A. (Box-folder 10: 62)
      - Schally, Andrew V., Dr. (Box-folder 10: 63)
      - Schipper, Lee (Box-folder 10: 64)
      - Schram, Martin, Mr. (Box-folder 10: 65)
      - Schriver, Dorothy, Ms (Box-folder 10: 66)
      - Schroll, Richard L., Mr. and Mrs. (Box-folder 10: 67)
      - Schultz, Robert Von, Mr. (Box-folder 10: 68)
      - Segerstedt, Rektor Torgny (Box-folder 10: 69)
      - Sehlin, Halvar, Mr. (Box-folder 10: 70)
      - Sellin, Ted, Mr. and Mrs. (Box-folder 10: 71)
      - Shannon, William V., Honorable (Box-folder 10: 72)
      - Shelp, Ronald K. (Box-folder 10: 73)
      - Sherwood, Bob (handwritten letter is enclosed) (Box-folder 10: 74)
      - Sigurd, Anthon, Mr. (Box-folder 10: 75)
      - Simon, Herbert A., Prof. (Box-folder 10: 76)
      - Singer, Isaac and Alma (Box-folder 10: 77)
      - Sjoberg, Stanley, The Rev. (Box-folder 10: 78)
      - Sjoquist, Eric, Mr. (Box-folder 10: 79)
      - Skaltsounis, Helen, Ms. (Box-folder 10: 80)
      - Slayton, William L., Mr. (Box-folder 10: 81)
      - Smith, David, Mr. (Box-folder 10: 82)
      - Smith, Frederick, Jr., Mr. (Box-folder 10: 83)
      - Smith, Howard N., Mr. (Box-folder 10: 84)
      - Smith, Lowell V., Mayor (Box-folder 10: 85)
      - Smith, Michael J. (Box-folder 10: 86)
      - Soder, Karin, Honorable (Box-folder 10: 87)
      - Soffe, David E., Mr. (Box-folder 10: 88)
      - Sohns, Ernest R. (Box-folder 10: 89)
      - Solarz, Stephen J., Honorable (Box-folder 10: 90)
      - Solomon, Herbert (Box-folder 10: 91)
      - Solomon, Richard H., Mr. (Box-folder 10: 92)
      - Sparring, Ake, Mr. (Box-folder 10: 93)
      - Spitzer, Jack J. (Box-folder 10: 94)
      - Staats, Elmer B., Mr. (Box-folder 10: 95)
      - Stadler, Walter E., Mr. (Box-folder 10: 96)
      - Stenkvist, Britt-Marie, Miss (Box-folder 10: 97)
      - St.Germain, Fernand J., Honorable (Box-folder 10: 98)
      - Stone, Deirdre, Ms. (Box-folder 10: 99)
      - Stromdahl, Bill, Mr. (Box-folder 10: 100)
      - Strauss, Harlan J., Dr. (Box-folder 10: 101)
      - Sundberg, Edward, Mr. and Mrs. (Box-folder 10: 102)
      - Svantesson, Nils (Box-folder 10: 103)
      - Svedberg, Bjorn, Mr. (Box-folder 10: 104)
      - Thompson, Llewellyn, Mrs. (Box-folder 11: 1)
      - Tigerschiold, Malcolm, Mr. (Box-folder 11: 2)
      - Totten, George, Prof. (Box-folder 11: 3)
      - Tunney, John, Mr. (Box-folder 11: 4)
      - Turisttrafikforbund, Stockholms (Box-folder 11: 5)
      - Turnquist, Dan, Mr. (Box-folder 11: 6)
      - Vance, Cyrus R., Honorable (Box-folder 11: 7)
      - Vardanega, Bruce (handwritten) (Box-folder 11: 8)
      - Vasquez, Anthony F. Dr., The Rev. (Box-folder 11: 9)
      - Vest, George S., Honorable (Box-folder 11: 10)
      - Vine, Richard D., Esquire (Box-folder 11: 11)
      - Voigt, Heinz, Ambassador, Mr. and Mrs. (Box-folder 11: 12)
      - Voll, Peter, Mr. (Box-folder 11: 13)
      - Wahlgren, Gunnar S. (Box-folder 11: 14)
      - Walgren, Gordon L. (Box-folder 11: 15)
      - Wall, Anders, Mr. (Box-folder 11: 16)
      - Wallenberg, Peter, Mr. (Box-folder 11: 17)
      - Wellons, Caroline (handwritten) (Box-folder 11: 18)
      - West, W.E. (Box-folder 11: 19)
      - Weteer, Gillis J., Honorable (Box-folder 11: 20)
      - Wheeler, John R., Mrs. (Box-folder 11: 21)
      - Widen, Albin, Dr. (Box-folder 11: 22)
      - Wilmink, Janet M. (Box-folder 11: 23)
      - Winberg, Claes-Ulrik, Mr. (Box-folder 11: 24)
      - Wise, Phil, Mr. (Box-folder 11: 25)
      - Wolcott, Phil (Box-folder 11: 26)
      - Wolff, Lester L., Honorable (Box-folder 11: 27)
      - Woods, Ronald E., Honorable (Box-folder 11: 28)
      - Zialcita, Lorenzo J. M., Mr. (Box-folder 11: 29)
    - Memoranda
      - Undated (Box-folder 11: 30)
      - January (Box-folder 11: 31)
      - February (Box-folder 11: 32)
      - March (Box-folder 11: 33)
      - April (Box-folder 11: 34)
      - May (Box-folder 11: 35)
      - June (Box-folder 11: 36)
      - July (Box-folder 11: 37)
      - August (Box-folder 11: 38)
      - September (Box-folder 11: 39)
      - October (Box-folder 11: 40)
      - November (Box-folder 11: 41)
      - December (Box-folder 11: 42)
    - Schedules
      - (telephone message is included), January (Box-folder 11: 43)
      - February (Box-folder 11: 44)
      - (telephone message is included), March (Box-folder 11: 45)
      - April (Box-folder 11: 46)
      - May (Box-folder 11: 47)
      - June (Box-folder 11: 48)
      - (handwritten notes are enclosed), July (Box-folder 11: 49)
      - August (Box-folder 11: 50)
      - September (Box-folder 11: 51)
      - October (Box-folder 11: 52)
      - (printed copy is enclosed), November (Box-folder 11: 53)
      - December (Box-folder 11: 54)
    - Notes (handwritten) (Box-folder 12: 1)
    - Newsletters (Box-folder 12: 2)
    - Press release (Box-folder 12: 3)
    - Telegrams
      - January (Box-folder 12: 4)
      - February (Box-folder 12: 5)
      - April (Box-folder 12: 6)
      - May (Box-folder 12: 7)
      - June (Box-folder 12: 8)
      - July (Box-folder 12: 9)
      - October (Box-folder 12: 10)
      - November (Box-folder 12: 11)
      - December (Box-folder 12: 12)
    - Clippings (Box-folder 12: 13)
    - Printed matter (Box-folder 12: 14)
  - 1979
    - Correspondence
      - Unidentified (Box-folder 12: 15)
      - General (Box-folder 12: 16)
      - Aarni, Brita, Ms. (Box-folder 12: 17)
      - Aberg, Carl Johan, Mr. (Box-folder 12: 18)
      - Acalin, David, Mr. (Box-folder 12: 19)
      - Ackerman, Karl D., Honorable (Box-folder 12: 20)
      - Ehnberg, G., Mr. (Box-folder 12: 21)
      - Ahnlund, Lars, Mr. (Box-folder 12: 22)
      - Akestam, Sten A.A., Mr. (Box-folder 12: 23)
      - Aldman, Margaret, Ms. (Box-folder 12: 24)
      - Alexander, N.P., Honorable (Box-folder 12: 25)
      - Allard, Henry, Honorable (Box-folder 12: 26)
      - Allen, James R., General (Box-folder 12: 27)
      - Anderson, Charles A. (Box-folder 12: 28)
      - Anderson, Harry W., Mr. (Box-folder 12: 29)
      - Anderson, Henry W., Mr. (Box-folder 12: 30)
      - Anderson, Wendell R., Honorable (Box-folder 12: 31)
      - Andrews, Mary E., Ms. (Box-folder 12: 32)
      - Armor, William, Mr. (Box-folder 12: 33)
      - Arnesen, Leif, Mr. (Box-folder 12: 34)
      - Bandler, Vivica, Ms. (Box-folder 12: 35)
      - Barnaby, Frank (Box-folder 12: 36)
      - Baydur, Mehmet, Honorable (Box-folder 12: 37)
      - Bengtsson, Ingvar, Mr. (Box-folder 12: 38)
      - Bergland, Bob, Honorable (Box-folder 12: 39)
      - Bergman, Margareta, Ms. (Box-folder 12: 40)
      - Bergman, Ralph M., Mr. (Box-folder 12: 41)
      - Bergstrom, Hans, Mr. (Box-folder 12: 42)
      - Bergstrom, Kiki, Ms. (Box-folder 12: 43)
      - Bingham, George H., Mr. (Box-folder 12: 44)
      - Blanco, Montwig, Ambassador (Box-folder 12: 45)
      - Blix, Hans, Honorable (Box-folder 12: 46)
      - Blum, Barbara, Ms. (Box-folder 12: 47)
      - Bxe, Alf, Mr. (Box-folder 12: 48)
      - Boethius, Maria-Pia, Ms. (Box-folder 12: 49)
      - Bonstrom, Margareta, Ms. (Box-folder 12: 50)
      - Bremer, Paul L. III, Esquire (Box-folder 12: 51)
      - Brown, Chris, Mr. (Box-folder 12: 52)
      - Brown, Herbert C., Prof. (Box-folder 12: 53)
      - Brown, Kenneth C., Ambassador (Box-folder 12: 54)
      - Bullough, William, Prof. (Box-folder 12: 55)
      - Butcher, Duane C., Mr. (Box-folder 12: 56)
      - Buxbaum, Charlotte, Ms. (Box-folder 12: 57)
      - Califano, Joseph A., Jr. (Box-folder 12: 58)
      - California Assembly Fellowship Program (Box-folder 12: 59)
      - Canney, Ada H. (Box-folder 12: 60)
      - Canney, Paul F. (Box-folder 12: 61)
      - Carl XVI Gustaf, King of Sweden (Box-folder 12: 62)
      - Carre-Magee, Virginia, Ms. (Box-folder 12: 63)
      - Childs, Mark, Mr. and Mrs. (Box-folder 12: 64)
      - Chin, Li-chen, His Excellency (Box-folder 12: 65)
      - Chiocco, Ralph, Mr. (Box-folder 12: 66)
      - Christopher, Warren, Honorable (Box-folder 12: 67)
      - Church, Frank, Honorable (Box-folder 12: 68)
      - Clifford, Clark, Esquire (Box-folder 12: 69)
      - Clough, Susan S., Ms. (note to President Carter is enclosed) (Box-folder 12: 70)
      - Coelho, Tony, Honorable (Box-folder 13: 1)
      - Cohen, Edward M. (Box-folder 13: 2)
      - Connelly, Patrick C., Mr. (Box-folder 13: 3)
      - Cooper, Kenneth J., Dr. (Box-folder 13: 4)
      - Cormack, Allan M., Prof. (Box-folder 13: 5)
      - Coughlan, Rob (handwritten letter) (Box-folder 13: 6)
      - Crane, Donald R., Jr., Mr. (Box-folder 13: 7)
      - Dance, Maurice (Box-folder 13: 8)
      - Danelius, Hans, Ambassador (Box-folder 13: 9)
      - Davis, John, Mr. and Mrs. (Box-folder 13: 10)
      - Deason, Robert, Mr. (Box-folder 13: 11)
      - Denmark, Bernhardt, Mr. (Box-folder 13: 12)
      - Dittberner, Job L., Mr. (Box-folder 13: 13)
      - Dobelle, Evan S. (Box-folder 13: 14)
      - Dockens, William S. III, Dr. (Box-folder 13: 15)
      - Doherty, R.P., Jr. (Box-folder 13: 16)
      - Domberger, Joseph H., Mr. (Box-folder 13: 17)
      - Donchi, Don J., Mr. (Box-folder 13: 18)
      - Dorr, Robert F., Mr. (Box-folder 13: 19)
      - Doty, James T., Mr. (Box-folder 13: 20)
      - Dubs, Adolph, Mrs. (Box-folder 13: 21)
      - Duncan, Glenn A., Mr. (Box-folder 13: 22)
      - Edgerton, Wallace B., Mr. (Box-folder 13: 23)
      - Eisele, Albert, Mr. (Box-folder 13: 24)
      - Ekman, Ernst, Prof. (Box-folder 13: 25)
      - Elderkin, Lannie (Box-folder 13: 26)
      - Elfmann, LeRoy (Box-folder 13: 27)
      - Ellinge, Barbro, Ms. (Box-folder 13: 28)
      - Engestang, Helge, Mr. (Box-folder 13: 29)
      - Entezam, Abbas Amir, Honorable (Box-folder 13: 30)
      - Ericson, Malte, Lieutenant-Colonel (Box-folder 13: 31)
      - Ericson, Richard S.S., J.D. (Box-folder 13: 32)
      - Eriksson, Gunnel, Ms. (Box-folder 13: 33)
      - Falldin, Thorbjorn, Honorable (Box-folder 13: 34)
      - Farber, Ulla, Mrs. (Box-folder 13: 35)
      - Fehrenbacher, Don, Prof. (Box-folder 13: 36)
      - Fischer, Karl Ingmar, Dr., Ambassador (Box-folder 13: 37)
      - Fleetwood, Carl Edvard, Baron (Box-folder 13: 38)
      - Francis, Albert A., Mr. (Box-folder 13: 39)
      - Francis, Les, Mr. (Box-folder 13: 40)
      - Fultz, Barbara, Ms. (Box-folder 13: 41)
      - Funseth, Robert L. (Box-folder 13: 42)
      - Garrett, Stephen A. (Box-folder 13: 43)
      - George Washington University (Box-folder 13: 44)
      - Gillespie, Robert W., Prof. (Box-folder 13: 45)
      - Girard, Marguerite M., Ms. (Box-folder 13: 46)
      - Giuffrida, Matthew R., Mr. (Box-folder 13: 47)
      - Glashow, Sheldon L., Prof. (Box-folder 13: 48)
      - Glasrud, Bruce A. (Box-folder 13: 49)
      - Goldfield, David R., Dr. (Box-folder 13: 50)
      - Gomperts, Robert E. (some handwritten notes and memoranda are enclosed) (Box-folder 13: 51)
      - Gramm, Phil, Honorable (Box-folder 13: 52)
      - Granum, Rex, Esquire (Box-folder 13: 53)
      - Gray, Norma and May (handwritten card) (Box-folder 13: 54)
      - Greenberg, Julee, Ms. (Box-folder 13: 55)
      - Griffin, Ruth, Mrs. (Box-folder 13: 56)
      - Gunnemo, Sven, Mr. (Box-folder 13: 57)
      - Gustafsson, Rolf, Mr. (Box-folder 13: 58)
      - Haggstrom, Sven (letter written in Swedish) (Box-folder 13: 59)
      - Hagopian, Caroline, Ms. (Box-folder 13: 60)
      - Haijlen-Rylander, Maud Li, Mrs. (Box-folder 13: 61)
      - Hakim, Maksum- ul, Ambassador (Box-folder 13: 62)
      - Halberg, Charles J.A., Prof. (Box-folder 13: 63)
      - Hamilton, William C. (Box-folder 13: 64)
      - Hammer, Armand, Dr. and Mrs. (Box-folder 13: 65)
      - Hammarsten, Elisabeth, Ms. (Box-folder 13: 66)
      - Hanes, Philip and Joan (handwritten) (Box-folder 13: 67)
      - Harris, Karen, Ms. (Box-folder 13: 68)
      - Hart, Gary, Honorable (Box-folder 13: 69)
      - Hasselblad, Erna, Mrs.(handwritten card) (Box-folder 13: 70)
      - Hassett, Frederick H., Mr. (Box-folder 13: 71)